http://www.chriscraftboats.com/terms-of-use/

TERMS OF USE
Terms of Use outlines your obligations when using our website. You can also review our Privacy Policy, which outlines our obligations and practices towards handling any personal information that you may provide to us.
1. Your Acceptance
Chris-Craft designs, standard features, optional equipment and all specifications are subject to change without notice, to improve reliability, function, design or for other reasons.  All images of our products and their components and accessories are prototype images. The images may reflect optional equipment and are subject to change without notice. All information presented herein is based on data and / or design that is available at the time of posting and is subject to change without notice. Some equipment and/or features may be unavailable when the boat enters production or when your boat is built.  Actual results of performance and other specifications may differ or vary with production models and may depend on selected options and trim levels.
Chris-Craft provides service to you subject to the following Terms of Use, which may be updated by us from time to time without notice to you. These Terms of Use constitute a binding agreement between Chris-Craft and you governing your use of the Website. By using and/or visiting the www.chriscraft.com Website or any other Websites owned by Chris-Craft (collectively the "Website"), you signify your assent to both these Terms of Use and the chriscraft.com Privacy Policy. You are only authorized only to use the Website if you agree to abide by all applicable laws and to these Terms of Use. Please read these Terms of Use carefully. If you do not agree to these Terms of Use, please do not use the Website.
2. Website Access
Chris-Craft hereby grants you permission to use the Website as set forth in these Terms of Use, provided that: (i) your use of the Website as permitted is solely for your personal, noncommercial use; (ii) you will not copy or distribute any part of the Website in any medium without Chris-Craft’s prior written authorization; (iii) you will not alter or modify any part of the Website other than as may be reasonably necessary to use the Website for its intended purpose; and (iv) you will otherwise comply with the terms and conditions of these Terms of Use.
In order to access some features of the Website, you will have the option to create an account. You are not allowed to use another user’s account without permission. When creating your account, you must provide accurate and complete information. You are solely responsible for the activity that occurs on your account, and you must keep your account password secure. You may change your password at any time by updating your Account Profile page. In addition, you agree to immediately notify Chriscraft.com of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security. Chris-Craft cannot and will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with this Section 2.
By registering with Chriscraft.com, you represent that you are of legal age to form a binding contract and are not a person barred by any laws from using the Chriscraft.com Website. You agree to provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself in all required fields of the registration form. If any of your information changes, you agree to update your registration information as soon as possible. If Chris-Craft suspects that your registration information is not complete, current, or accurate, or that you have otherwise violated these Terms of Use, your account may be subject to suspension or termination, and you may be barred from using the Chriscraft.com Website.
You agree not to use or launch any automated system, including without limitation, "robots," "spiders," or similar technological devices or programs, that access the Website in a manner that sends more request messages to the Chriscraft.com servers in a given period of time than a human can reasonably produce in the same period by using a conventional on-line web browser. Notwithstanding the foregoing, Chris-Craft grants the operators of public search engines permission to use spiders to copy materials from the Website for the sole purpose of creating publicly available searchable indices of the materials, but not caches or archives of such materials. Chris-Craft reserves the right to revoke these exceptions either generally or in specific cases, in its sole discretion.
You agree not to collect or use any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") including without limitation account names, email addresses, or other User Submissions (as defined below), from the Website, nor use the communication systems provided by the Website for any commercial solicitation purposes, including without limitation to solicit, for commercial purposes, any users of the Website.
3. The Chriscraft.com Website
These Terms of Use apply to all users of the Website, including users who contribute information, ideas, and other materials or services on the Website. The Website may contain links to third party websites that are not owned or controlled by Chris-Craft. Chris-Craft has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party websites. By using the Website, you specifically release Chris-Craft from any and all liability arising from your use of any third-party website.
4. Intellectual Property Rights
The content on the Website, including without limitation, the text, graphics, and photos created by and for Chris-Craft, interactive features ("Content") and the trademarks, service marks and logos contained therein ("Marks"), is owned by or licensed to Chris-Craft, subject to copyright and other intellectual property rights under United States and foreign laws and international conventions. Content on the Website is provided to you AS IS for your information and personal use only and may not be used, copied, reproduced, distributed, transmitted, broadcast, displayed, sold, licensed, or otherwise exploited for any purpose whatsoever without the prior written consent of Chris-Craft or as expressly provided herein. Chris-Craft reserves all rights not expressly granted in and to the Website and the Content contained therein.
You agree to not engage in the use, copying, or distribution of any of the Content other than expressly permitted herein for any commercial purposes. If you download or print a copy of the Content for personal use, you must retain all copyright and other proprietary notices contained thereon. You agree not to circumvent, disable or otherwise interfere with security related features of the Website or features that prevent or restrict use or copying of any Content or enforce limitations on use of the Website or the Content therein.
5. Modifications to the Website
Chris-Craft reserves the right at any time and from time to time to modify or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, the Website (or any part thereof) with or without notice. Chris-Craft shall not be liable to you or to any third party for any modification, suspension or discontinuance of the Website.
6. Termination
Chris-Craft may, under certain circumstances and without prior notice, immediately terminate your Chriscraft.com account and access to the Website and any other Chriscraft.com services. Cause for such termination shall include, but not be limited to: (a) breaches or violations of the Terms of Use other incorporated agreements or guidelines; (b) requests by law enforcement or other government agencies; (c) a request by you (self-initiated account deletions); (d) discontinuance or material modification to the Website (or any part thereof); (e) unexpected technical or security issues or problems; (f) extended periods of inactivity; (g) engagement by you in fraudulent or illegal activities; and/or (h) nonpayment of any fees owed by you in connection with the Website or any other Chriscraft.com product. Termination of your Chriscraft.com account includes: (a) removal of access to all pages within the Website; (b) deletion of your password and all related information, files and materials; and (c) barring of further use of the Website. Further, you agree that all terminations for cause shall be made in Chris-Craft sole discretion and that Chris-Craft shall not be liable to you or any third party for any termination of your account, any associated email address, or access to the Website.
7. Warranty Disclaimer
YOU AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE SHALL BE AT YOUR SOLE RISK. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, CHRIS-CRAFT, AND ANY PARENT, SUBSIDIARY, AFFILIATE, DIRECTOR, OFFICER, EMPLOYEE, LICENSOR, DISTRIBUTOR, SUPPLIER, AGENT, RESELLER, OWNER, OR OPERATOR OF CHRISCRAFT.COM, DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, IN CONNECTION WITH THE WEBSITE AND YOUR USE THEREOF.   MAKES NO WARRANTIES OR REPRESENTATIONS ABOUT THE ACCURACY OR COMPLETENESS OF THE WEBSITE’S CONTENT OR THE CONTENT OF ANY SITES LINKED TO THIS SITE AND ASSUMES NO LIABILITY OR RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY (I) ERRORS, MISTAKES, OR INACCURACIES OF CONTENT, (II) PERSONAL INJURY OR PROPERTY DAMAGE, OF ANY NATURE WHATSOEVER, RESULTING FROM YOUR ACCESS TO AND USE OF THE WEBSITE, (III) ANY UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR USE OF OUR SECURE SERVERS AND/OR ANY AND ALL PERSONAL INFORMATION STORED THEREIN, (IV) ANY INTERRUPTION OR CESSATION OF TRANSMISSION TO OR FROM THE WEBSITE, (IV) ANY BUGS, VIRUSES, TROJAN HORSES, OR THE LIKE WHICH MAY BE TRANSMITTED TO OR THROUGH OUR WEBSITE BY ANY THIRD PARTY, AND/OR (V) ANY ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN ANY CONTENT OR FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE OF ANY KIND INCURRED AS A RESULT OF THE USE OF ANY CONTENT POSTED, EMAILED, TRANSMITTED, OR OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE VIA THE WEBSITE. CHRISCRAFT.COM DOES NOT WARRANT, ENDORSE, GUARANTEE, OR ASSUME RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY HYPERLINKED WEBSITE OR OTHER PROMOTION, AND CHRISCRAFT.COM WILL NOT BE A PARTY TO OR IN ANY WAY BE RESPONSIBLE FOR MONITORING ANY TRANSACTION BETWEEN YOU AND THIRD-PARTY PROVIDERS OF PRODUCTS OR SERVICES. NO ADVICE OR INFORMATION, WHETHER ORAL OR WRITTEN, OBTAINED BY YOU FROM CHRIS-CRAFT OR THROUGH OR FROM THE SERVICE SHALL CREATE ANY WARRANTY NOT EXPRESSLY STATED IN THE TERMS OF USE. AS WITH THE PURCHASE OF A PRODUCT OR SERVICE THROUGH ANY MEDIUM OR IN ANY ENVIRONMENT, YOU SHOULD USE YOUR BEST JUDGMENT AND EXERCISE CAUTION WHERE APPROPRIATE.
8. Limitation of Liability
IN NO EVENT SHALL CHRISCRAFT.COM, OR ANY PARENT, SUBSIDIARY, AFFILIATE, DIRECTOR, OFFICER, EMPLOYEE, LICENSOR, DISTRIBUTOR, SUPPLIER, AGENT, RESELLER, OWNER, OR OPERATOR OF CHRISCRAFT.COM, BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES WHATSOEVER RESULTING FROM ANY (I) ERRORS, MISTAKES, OR INACCURACIES OF CONTENT, (II) PERSONAL INJURY OR PROPERTY DAMAGE, OF ANY NATURE WHATSOEVER, RESULTING FROM YOUR ACCESS TO AND USE OF OUR WEBSITE, (III) ANY UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR USE OF OUR SECURE SERVERS AND/OR ANY AND ALL PERSONAL INFORMATION STORED THEREIN, (IV) ANY INTERRUPTION OR CESSATION OF TRANSMISSION TO OR FROM OUR WEBSITE, (IV) ANY BUGS, VIRUSES, TROJAN HORSES, OR THE LIKE, WHICH MAY BE TRANSMITTED TO OR THROUGH OUR WEBSITE BY ANY THIRD PARTY, AND/OR (V) ANY ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN ANY CONTENT OR FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE OF ANY KIND INCURRED AS A RESULT OF YOUR USE OF ANY CONTENT POSTED, EMAILED, TRANSMITTED, OR OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE VIA THE WEBSITE, WHETHER BASED ON WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT, OR ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY, AND WHETHER OR NOT THE COMPANY IS ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. THE FOREGOING LIMITATION OF LIABILITY SHALL APPLY TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW IN THE APPLICABLE JURISDICTION.
The Website is controlled and offered by Chris-Craft from its facilities in the United States of America. Chris-Craft makes no representations that the Website is appropriate or available for use in other locations. Those who access or use the Website from other jurisdictions do so at their own volition and are responsible for compliance with local law.
9. Indemnity
You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless Chris-Craft, and any parent, subsidiary, affiliate, director, officer, employee, licensor, distributor, supplier, agent, reseller, owner, or operator of Chriscraft.com, from and against any and all claims, damages, obligations, losses, liabilities, costs or debt, and expenses (including but not limited to attorney’s fees) arising from: (i) your use of and access to the Website; (ii) your violation of any term of these Terms of Use; or (iii) your violation of any third party right, including without limitation any copyright, property, or privacy right. This defense and indemnification obligation will survive these Terms of Use and your use of the Website.
10. Ability to Accept Terms of Use
You affirm that you are either 18 years of age or older, or an emancipated minor, or possess legal parental or guardian consent, and are fully able and competent to enter into the terms, conditions, obligations, affirmations, representations, and warranties set forth in these Terms of Use, and to abide by and comply with these Terms of Use. Chriscraft.com is not intended for children under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use the Chriscraft.com Website.
11. Assignment
These Terms of Use, and any rights and licenses granted hereunder, may not be assigned, transferred, delegated, and sublicensed by you, but may be assigned, transferred, delegated, and sublicensed by Chris-Craft without restriction.
12. Copyright Notice
The Chris-Craft Website is © 2019, Chris-Craft – All Rights Reserved and no portion of the Website may be copied, reproduced, transmitted, derived, or otherwise used for any purpose without the prior written permission of Chris-Craft.
13. Trademarks
All of the Chriscraft.com trademarks are owned by Chris-Craft and may not be used for any purpose without the prior written permission of Chris-Craft.
14. General
If any provision of these Terms of Use is deemed invalid by a court of competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining provisions of these Terms of Use, which shall remain in full force and effect. No waiver of any term of these Terms of Use shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term or any other term, and Chris-Craft failure to assert any right or provision under these Terms of Use shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision. Chris-Craft reserves the right to amend these Terms of Use at any time in its sole discretion and without prior notice, which shall take effect upon posting to the Website. It is your responsibility to review these Terms of Use for any changes. Your use of the Website following any amendment of these Terms of Use will signify your assent to and acceptance of its revised terms. You agree that any cause of action arising out of or related to the Website must commence within one (1) year after the cause of action accrues. Otherwise, such cause of action is permanently barred.
15. Violations of These Terms of Use
Please report any violations of the Terms of Use to info@chriscraft.com. Please state the reasons for your concern and provide a link to the User Content or, if appropriate, the behavior in question. Upon receiving such a report of a possible violation, Chris-Craft in its sole discretion may investigate the matter and take such action as chriscraft.com determines to be appropriate.
16. Privacy Policy
View Chris-Craft Privacy Policy.
17. Updates to Terms of Use
Terms of Use updated January 2019
Our website uses cookies to collect information. Read more on our privacy policy here.
close
